

Deok-Kyeong (DK), JANG +82 10 2898 1777 Seoul/Korea dk.jang@movin3d.com

personal page in linkedin og github

ABOUT

I'm a Co-founder/CTO at movin and also a Postdoc in Motion Computing Lab at KAIST. Before that, I interned at Meta Reality Labs. My research goal is to improve the quality of digital character motion in computer graphics and AR/VR systems using deep learning methods. I currently focus on the real-time motion characterization and 3D full-body motion capture using a single LiDAR.

EDUCATION _

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2017-2022 / South Korea

Ph.D. in Computer Graphics / Motion Computing Laboratory / Advisor: Sung-Hee Lee

Research on virtual motion stylization/characterization, motion synthesis/control and manifold space.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2015-2017 / South Korea

M.S. in Computer Graphics / Motion Computing Laboratory / Advisor: Sung-Hee Lee

• Research on regression-based landmark detection of Human Models.

Korea Advanced Institute of Science and Technology (KAIST)

2009-2015 / South Korea

B.S. in Physics and Mathematics

• Research on modeling the prey-predator system.

PUBLICATION

3D Motion Capture in Real-Time using a Single LiDAR [working title]

2023 / under review

Computer Grahpics Forum (CGF) / Pacific graphics 2023

Deok-Kyeong Jangt, Dongseok Yangt, Deokyun Jangt, Byeoli Choit and Sung-Hee Lee

Motion Characterization in Real-Time [working title]

2023 / under review

ACM SIGGRAPH ASIA 2023

Deok-Kyeong Jang, Yuting Ye, Jungdam Won and Sung-Hee Lee

Motion Puzzle: Arbitrary Motion Style Transfer by Body Part

2022

ACM Transactions on Graphics (TOG) / ACM SIGGRAPH 2022

Deok-Kyeong Jang, Soomin Park and Sung-Hee Lee

Diverse Motion Stylization for Multiple Style Domains

2021

via Spatial-Temporal Graph-Based Generative Model

Proceedings of the ACM on Computer Graphics and Interactive Techniques (PACMCGIT) / SCA Soomin Park, Deok-Kyeong Jang, and Sung-Hee Lee

Constructing Human Motion Manifold With Sequential Networks

2020

Computer Grahpics Forum (CGF) / Eurographics 2021

Deok-Kyeong Jang and Sung-Hee Lee

Regression-Based Landmark Detection on Dynamic Human Models

2017

Computer Grahpics Forum (CGF) / Pacific graphics

Deok-Kyeong Jang and Sung-Hee Lee

WORK EXPERIENCE

CTO / Co-founder 2023.03 - now / movin

Product: 3D full-body motion capture solution using a single LiDAR.

• Developed real-time full-body motion capture framework based on a single LiDAR, incorporating global translation tracking. Constructing a high-quality dataset featuring diverse subjects, containing synchronized LiDAR point cloud and optical motion capture data for a wide range of actions.

Research Science Intern

2022.05 - 2022.10 / Meta Reality Labs, Redmond, USA

Manager: Yuting Ye, Research Scientist in Gemini team from Meta Reality Labs

Collaborators: Dr.Jungdam Won, Research Scientist from Meta AI

• Research on motion characterization in real-time, enhancement of motion style transfer and retargeting with various input sensors.

PROJECTS

Motion tracking and characterization research for virtual avatars

2022 - 2023

Meta Platforms Technologies

• As a researcher of the project, developed real-time motion characterization framework for virtual avatars.

Study of styled motion generation for non-verbal communication of virtual human agents

2020 - 2022

National Research Foundation of Korea

• As a leading researcher of the project, developed humanoid agent's appearance-style customizable motion generation framework.

Development of 4D Reconstruction and Dynamic Deformable Action Model based Hyper Realistic Service Technology

2017 - 2021

Ministry of Science, ICT and Future Planning, Giga Korea Project

• As a leading researcher of the project, developed motion style transfer method and plugins to automatically generate stylized motion.

Development of Simulation Software for Human Body-Sport Gear Complex for Rapidly Prototyping Customized Sports Gear

2015 - 2017

Ministry of Culture, Sports and Tourism

• As a main developer of the project, developed an sports gear modeling technique that fits the personalized foot shape and sports gear interaction.

PAPER REVIEWER

SIGGRAPH, SIGGRAPH ASIA, Pacific Graphics, Computer Graphics Forum, IEEE Transactions on Visualization and Computer Graphics (TVCG)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages Python | C# | C/C++ | Matlab

Operating Systems Mac OS X | Linux/Unix | Windows

Frameworks & Libraries PyTorch | Tensorflow | Eigen | igl | Numpy | etc.

Tools Unity | Blender | Docker System | etc.